



Eliecer Sánchez Mora

Nationality: Venezuelan Date of birth: 05/08/1995 Gender: Male

Capacita Spiral Spiral

Email address: eliecer.sanchez47@gmail.com

© Whatsapp Messenger: +356 7954 8102

in LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/eliecer-sanchez-mora-22688a26a

Website: https://eliecersm-portfolio.netlify.app

• Home: Triq Had Dingli Aparment, RBT 9023 Rabat (Malta)

ABOUT ME

Goal-oriented individual with a pleasant personality and a tenacity that knows no restrictions. I can be a multitasking person, willing to meet the goal of the company and work as a team.

As a Fullstack developer, i prefer both frontend and backend, i realy like working with JavaScript (libraries, framework (Reactjs and Nodejs), and i keep up learning everyday. based on my past experience into the programming world, i manage good logic and work under preassure, i'm creative and with a possitive mentality to resolve problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Reactis and Nodejs developer

Freelancer and Self-Taught [02/12/2021 - Current]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

- Development with JavaScript library React and developing UI, improving my skills building projects
- Development API, services and more with JavaScript runtime environment NodelS and it's frameworks

JavaScript

Self -Taught [02/01/2022 - 02/04/2022]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

- Development and studies of vanilla JavaScript, building small projects

Database suport and Administrator (MySQL)

Lara State Goberment [01/05/2018 - 31/08/2018]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

- manage Database for worker assistance system
- ensure data integrity

Java SE developer

Lara State Goberment [01/05/2018 - 01/09/2018]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

- Improve worker assintance system built in Java SE

Java SE developer

University Institute of Technology "Antonio José de Sucre" and then Freelancer [02/01/2019 -

31/12/2019]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

- I have developed an Automated system for managing graduates of my university

- As freelacer i developed an Automated inventory system for a client

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

University Technician in Computer Science

University Institute of Technology "Antonio José de Sucre" [15/09/2014 - 01/02/2019]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

Website: http://www.utsbarguisimeto.edu.ve/

Programming Logic and Java SE level 1 course

CADIf1 [21/08/2016 - 26/10/2016]

City: Baquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

Website: https://cadif1.com/

English Conversation 1 Course

Westminster [22/11/2017 – 22/03/2019]

City: Barquisimeto **Country:** Venezuela

Website: https://gelvez.com.ve/barquisimeto/idiomas/27625-idiomas-westminster.html

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Spanish

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

VisalStudio Code / Postman API / Mongo DB and PostgreSQL / Reactjs / Nodejs / Social Media / Tailwind CSS / Socket.io / Express js

APTITUDES

Good communication, empathy and camaraderie

Analytical skills and work under pressure

Ability to solve problems

Willingness to learn and risk

Having a good business sense

Ability to handle criticism